[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been proposed that before the evolution of leaves, plants had the photosynthetic apparatus on which parts?", "correct_answer": "stems", "incorrect_answers": ["roots", "buds", "none of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of movie is the 1987 Stanley Kubrick film Full Metal Jacket?", "correct_answer": "War movie", "incorrect_answers": ["Sports movie", "Horror movie", "Comedy movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two kinds of vehicles does the singer want to buy in the new car freecreditreport.com commercial?", "correct_answer": "a convertible and an SUV", "incorrect_answers": ["a Hummer and a scooter", "a Tesla and a Versa", "a Lexus and a Harley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marijuana is known by many names, including all of these but one. Which is the odd name?", "correct_answer": "Janu", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary Jane", "Weed", "Pot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast is Mach 1?", "correct_answer": "1207 kilometers per hour", "incorrect_answers": ["1207 meters per hour", "1207 feet per second", "1207 miles per hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The XY chromosome(s) determines that an embryo is developed into a baby girl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Lost Boys, where did Sam, Michael and their mother live before moving to Santa Carla?", "correct_answer": "Phoenix, Arizona", "incorrect_answers": ["Austin, Texas", "Roswell, New Mexico", "Cleveland, Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What classic song does Willie sing during the opening credits to the movie Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom?", "correct_answer": "Anything Goes!", "incorrect_answers": ["Oklahoma!", "White Christmas", "Thats Amore!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do cats always want in when they are out, and out when thery are in?", "correct_answer": "To re-mark their scent", "incorrect_answers": ["To annoy you", "Because they have pent-up energy", "Because they are bored"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jean Smart stars in the movie Sweet Home Alabama as Jakes mother Stella. She has since starred again with Mary Lynn Rajskub in what popular television series?", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["Prison Break", "CSI", "Numb3rs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can you put movies and TV shows on your iPod?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character in the film A Christmas Story who questions The Old Man about the leg lamp?", "correct_answer": "Swede", "incorrect_answers": ["Mole", "Frank", "Bob"]}]